<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kaman Phamdo</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/home/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/home/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 21:34:43 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 21:34:43 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.5.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seattle: Spring Break 2018</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt; Over spring break, Jake and I embarked on our first trip across the
country to one of my favorite cities - Seattle! Our first stop was the 
Seattle Space Needle, which is currently being renovated to an all 
glass design. Luckily, it was open to the public during the short time we 
were visiting. Even though we were surrounded by construction and unable
to eat at the rotating restaurant, it was really cool to see the Space Needle
during a significant time in its history. The view of the city from the 
observation deck definitely did not disappoint.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/home/images/2018-03-22/needle-view.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Next, we visited the Chihuly Garden and Glass museum. This was most likely
my favorite attraction included in the Seattle City Pass. Chihuly was
a prolific artist, and we were able to see a lot of his work throughout the
city. I was extremely impressed by the glass blowing demonstration, where we
observed the entire process of creating a glass bowl. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/home/images/2018-03-22/glass.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; The next day, we went to the Seattle Aquarium. It was nothing new for me
since I had been there before, but I did enjoy seeing the cute sea otters. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/home/images/2018-03-22/wheel.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Afterward, we decided to take a ride on the Great Wheel. It seemed a little
pricey at first, but we ended up getting about 4-5 spins. I think it was worth
it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/home/images/2018-03-22/wheel-selfie.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; It was quite romantic, and we were able to enjoy some beautiful views of
the city skyline and the waterfront. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/home/images/2018-03-22/wheel-view.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; We also went on the Argosy Harbor Cruise. This was the perfect activity to
take a break after a long day of walking and get a lot of cool photos of
Seattle from the water. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/home/images/2018-03-22/boat-view.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Of course, we had to visit Pike Place Market and try bunch of different
foods. I had the famous New England Clam Chowder and Jake had his first char
siu bao from Mee Sum. We also tried some delicious pastry goods from
Piroshky Piroshky, a Russian bakery. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; The following day, we went to the Woodland Park Zoo. It was actually quite
an impressive zoo with a lot of animals. I also learned a fun fact: adult penguins
have a stripe on their neck, while chicks do not!
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/home/images/2018-03-22/zoo.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; That afternoon, we went to the Seattle Japanese Garden. It was really pretty
and the weather was absolutely gorgeous, which was surprising considering the snow
storms going on back home. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/home/images/2018-03-22/garden.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; I think one of the biggest highlights of our trip was eating dinner at Din
Tai Fung. They are famous for their delicious soup dumplings (xiao long bao),
and they definitely live up to the hype. I may or may not have come to Seattle just so
I could eat there... &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; On the final day of our trip, we did Bill Spiedel's Underground Tour.
I highly recommend this tour if you are interested in learning about the
history of Seattle. It was extremely interesting and entertaining, and our tour
guide told a lot of funny stories. We spent the remainder of the day 
wandering around the International District. It was a pretty good day, 
because Jake got the amazing news that he passed his job interview and was 
getting a job offer! We celebrated by eating Thai style hot pot for dinner. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; This trip was my first attempt at travel journaling. I am really glad 
that I documented it because I definitely don't want to forget it! 
I had so much fun and I can't wait for my next adventure! &lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 09:46:52 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/home/blog/2018/seattle/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/home/blog/2018/seattle/</guid>
        
        
        <category>travel</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
